{
    "subject": "resource/OrangeScape",
    "predicate": "property/industry",
    "object": "resource/Cloud_computing",
    "human_readable": "OrangeScape is in the industry of Cloud computing.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9819203019142151,
            "question": "Name a few competitors of OrangeScape in the cloud computing industry."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9195840954780579,
            "question": "Is OrangeScape a company that provides cloud services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8581421971321106,
            "question": "What industry is OrangeScape involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6379006505012512,
            "question": "What type of technology does OrangeScape work with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2873077094554901,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a product or service offered by OrangeScape?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22774791717529297,
            "question": "What is the future outlook for the cloud computing industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18967868387699127,
            "question": "What are some common applications of cloud computing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14717015624046326,
            "question": "How has cloud computing changed the way businesses operate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12401983141899109,
            "question": "What are the benefits of using cloud computing services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09681948274374008,
            "question": "What are some security concerns related to cloud computing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=OrangeScape is in the industry of Cloud computing.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7101_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the benefits of using cloud computing services?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7101_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has cloud computing changed the way businesses operate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7101_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common applications of cloud computing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7101_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7101_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7101_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7101_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7101_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7101_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7101_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7101_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7101_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7101_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7101_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's the evaluation:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nReasoning:\n\n* The documents mention that OrangeScape is a cloud pioneer based in India and offers SaaS solutions, which implies that it operates in the industry of Cloud computing.\n* The text also highlights OrangeScape's ability to build portable business applications that can run on various cloud infrastructures, further supporting its involvement in the Cloud computing industry.\n* Additionally, the partnership between OrangeScape and Eucalyptus is mentioned, which involves providing a complete cloud platform solution starting from private cloud, spanning into hybrid model, and running PaaS on top of it. This suggests that OrangeScape is indeed involved in the Cloud computing industry."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references that support OrangeScape being in the cloud computing industry. For example, they mention that OrangeScape offers a Visual Platform as a Service (PaaS), helps companies develop portable business applications for various cloud infrastructures, and works with Eucalyptus to offer private PaaS solutions."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}